Christophe A. MADOZ

www.coderfoundry.com/christophemadoz

FRAMEWORKS & PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

HTML5 CSS3

JavaScript/ES6

JQuery

Bootstrap

.NET

C#

 MVC

ASP.NET

SQL & Bash

LINQ

Xamarin

WebAPI

VΒ

PHP

AngularJS

C/C++

Java

Python

CODER

1231 Shields Road, Suite 5 Kernersville, NC 27284 (336) 231-8632

partnerships@coderfoundry.com

This resume contains information furnished by the candidate and has not been independently verified by Coder Foundry, LLC.

This information is privileged, confidential, and to be used solely by the individual and entity to which it has been submitted.

EDUCATION

University of North Carolina Greensboro, B.S. Computer Science *Greensboro, NC · 2017*

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Coder Foundry, Web Software Engineer

Kernersville, NC · July 2019-September 2019

- Created three primary projects, including:
 - 1. A portfolio site using C#, MVC, HTML5, CSS3, BOOTSTRAP, JS & jQuery.
 - 2. A Financial Portal implemented in three phases. Phase 1: an MVC Web Application, Phase 2: a Web Service that utilizes Swagger and Swashbuckle for integrated testing, Phase 3: A cross platform Xamarin Mobile Application.
 - 3. Fully designed and developed a multi-functional issue tracker web application, implementing enhanced roles & security, which also used a Code First Relational database designed and modeled in SQL Server. Technologies used include: .Net Framework v. 4.6.1, MVC5, C#, LINQ, SQL, Entity Framework, jQuery DataTables.

Madoz Digital, Developer

2014-Present

- Created websites for small businesses using ASP.NET MVC 5, C#, MS SQL server 2016.
- Developed a web-based database management system for campground business to track clients' information and reservations using HTML 5, JavaScript, AngularJS 4, CSS, Bootstrap 3.3.6, MVC, JSON, PHP, MySQL, WAMP.
- Managed all phases of a mid size HVAC company database system development, including designing, implementation, testing, and post-launch support using VB6, C#.NET, ADO.NET, MySQL, Crystal Report 2008.

Madoz Digital, Desktop Support

2000-Present

- Provided LAN design, network administration, and network troubleshooting for small businesses. Cisco IOS 12.4-15.0
- Diagnosed and resolved software and hardware incidents for desktops, laptops and tablets.
- Resolved incidents and upgraded different types of software and hardware. Resolved incidents with printers, copiers and scanners. Installed and configured industrial printers for banks and retail stores.